Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
- Audiotapes
  - Marriage of Figaro, Mozart, Gilly Dinh, Baritone, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_205; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Martha (Flotow) Metropolitan, 02/25/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_166; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Mascagni; W. Roger; Doolittle; B. Jones; Douglas Fairbanks Sr.; Gen. MacArthur; Dvorak; Flagstad; Peron, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_547; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 40)
  - Masked Ball, Verdi, Metropolitan Peerce, (Part 1), 02/28/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_036; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Masked Ball, Verdi, Metropolitan Peerce, (Part 2), 02/28/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_037; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Masked Ball; Requiem Verdi, 11/23/1940; bell_brothers_tapes_187; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Mass in D Minor (Cherubini); Sis Hopkins; The Barrier (Meyerowitz-Langst on Hughes); Selma Kurz, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_155; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Maurice Chevalieri; Flying Dutchman, Wagner, Metropolitan, (Part 1), 03/05/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_197; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Maurice Chevalieri; Flying Dutchman, Wagner, Metropolitan, (Part 2), 03/05/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_198; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Maytime Nelson Eddy and J. Mac D., undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_099 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Maytime; Lullaby of Broadway; Riccardo Stracciari; Louise, Maugham; Czar Und Zimmermann, Lortzig; Acis and Galatea, Handel, Sutherland, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_417; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Medea - Leinsdorf - Rexroth - Venus and Adonis - Republic - Crosby - Waller - M-24 Tank - Haeket, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_636; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Meet Me in St. Louis TV, 04/26/1959; "bell_brothers_tapes_020 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Meistersinger, Metropolitan Opera, Vaughn Meader; Niagara, Marilyn Monroe, 01/05/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_561; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Merchant of Venice Orson Wells Anthony Eden- J.D. Rockefeller, Sr. - Howard Huges; Alabama Dus- Edna St. Vincent Milay - Ballad for Americans - Mme Chiang - Kai- Shek; W. Churchill - Julius Caesar - Nuremberg Hanging - Edwin Markham, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_153; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Merchant of Venice Renard (Stravinsky) Mavra Works by Stravinsky (from old 78s), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_458; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Merchant of Venice, Castelnuovo; Tedesco; Volpone, Burt; Watt Tyler, Busch; La Donna Serpente, Cassella, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_519; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Merry Mount (Part 2), 1934; bell_brothers_tapes_049; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Merry Mount (Part 1), 1934; bell_brothers_tapes_048; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Mikado Acoustics, Gilbert and Sullivan, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_470; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous Forgotten Music and Toscanini, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_344; 1/2 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous Personalities - (Taft; Sother; etc.), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_480; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Personalities - Bryan - Kings, etc., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_481; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Personalities - Coffee Cantata and Amore Traditore; Raoul Guillome - Lillian Russell Film Helge Roswaenge - Frank Munn - Robert Oppenheimer, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_484; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Personalities - Einstein - Edison, etc., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_482; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Vocals (Classical), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_577; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous Vocals (Classical), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_578; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Missa Brevis (Kodaly) - Piano Music - (Scriabin) Salome Metropolitan - WNYC Concert, 02/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_351; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Missa Solemnis (Beethoven) Ayn Rand - Losteria Portoghese, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_290; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Moses (Rossini) The Regatta (Rossini) Comical Duetto Between Two Cats (Rossini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_685; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Moses (Rossini) The Regatta (Rossini) Comical Duetto Between Two Cats (Rossini), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_686; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Mother Wore Tights film, Betty Grable, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_030; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Mother Wore Tights film, Betty Grable, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_031; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3)
  - Music Boxes, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_081; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - My Sister Eileen, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_248; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - N.Y. Brass Quintet Haslemere Festival Louis Armstrong War and Peace; (Prokofieff) - G. Zenatello and Amato, 06/15/1963; 06/16/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_601; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Nabucco (Verdi), 1960; bell_brothers_tapes_164; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Nabucco (Verdi), 12/03/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_165; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Nasser; McCormack; Frijsh; Tunisia; Teyte-Dien Bien Fu; Frost; Schumann-Heink; Sound Effects (war), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_083; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Navy Blues Night Train to Memphis Tin Pan Alley Ruth Draper, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_154; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Neffru - Egmont; Is Everybody happy, Frieda Leider; Cries of London; Cosi Fan Tutte; Sacco and Vanzetti, 06/21/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_105; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - Nelson Eddy; Perry Como; M. Garden; Pygmalion; W. Earle, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_545; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - New Moon - Eddy and Macdonald - Jerry Lewis; Andrew Carnegie - Nelson Rockefeller, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_478; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 35)
  - New York Scrap Book (Demi-Dozen), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_126; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 9)
  - Night and Day Film - Yearling Film- Frieda Hempel- Subways are for Sleeping -Nelson Eddy - Dinah Shore- Main Street to Broadway Film, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_316; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Nikita Khrushchev, three hours interview on Open End TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_109; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 8)
  - No Business Like Show Business - Aida (L. Welitch)- Two Widows (Smetana)- Danny Kaye- Jap. Song, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_285; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Norman Corwin - Spanish Poetry - Princess Margaret - Duvalier - J. Bubble Here Come Coeds - Michael Bohnen- Always in My Heart; Ellington - Ella Fitzgerald, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_642; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Nuremberg Trials (from Film), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_162; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Oberon, Fidelio; Sonnambula, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_446; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Octet Hindemith Septet Beethoven, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_243; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Oedipus at Colonus (Sophocles) Dream Music (Gigli) Vienna festival, 1961; bell_brothers_tapes_337; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Oedipus Enesco Romeo and Juliet Zandonai - Elizabeth Schwartzkopf, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_261; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Oedipus Rex (Stravinsky) Voix Humaine (Poulenc)-Dangerous Nan McGrew - Helen Kane - Robin Hood - Bitter Sweet - Stork Club - Humoresque, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_287; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - Oedipus Rex, Stravinsky; The Lesbian, Dino Borgioli; Shooting in House of Representatives, Gov. Munoz Marin, Rep. Joe Martin, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_148; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Of Thee I Sing (Gershwin), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_339; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Old Fashioned Girl; Two Tickets to Broadway; Born to Sing; Man About Town, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_156; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Olimpia Boronat- Leon Escalais - Sholem Aleichem - Lone Star Trail - T. Roosevelt - Sigrid Arnoldson, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_461; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 33)
  - Olive Fremstad; Guerrina Fabbri; E. Schwartwkopf; Sancho Panca; Jolson Battistini, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_533; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - On the Riviera (Danny Kaye) - Poros (handel) La Fanciulla Del West (Metropolitan), 01/06/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_360; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Ondine; Dean Martin - TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_245; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Ondine; Dean Martin - TV, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_246; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Opening of Lincoln Center, Bebe Ruth; Ride Em Cowboy; Rumba, Herbert Witherspoon, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_512; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Opera by Marschner; Der Wein, Berg; Baron Von Munchausen; Symphony No. 7, Haydn; Maria Golovin, Menotti, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_528; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Operatic Vocals - Sadko (Rimsky - Korsakoff) Fats Waller - Victor Unreleased test pressings, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_604; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Orfeo and Eurydice (Gluck) Metropolitan Flatt and Scruggs - Love for Three Oranges (Prokofieff), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_367; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Orfeo and Euridice (Haydn); Western Hemisphere, 1961; bell_brothers_tapes_192; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Orlando, Handel; Helen; Watts;, Contr.; Stalin; Gagarin; Water carrier, Cherubini; L'Aiglon, Ibert; Honegger; Nikita Krustchev; Sgambati, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_629; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Otello - Metropolitan Opera (Part 2), 01/18/1941; bell_brothers_tapes_075; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Otello - Metropolitan Opera (Part 1), 01/18/1941; bell_brothers_tapes_073; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - Over Here Walter Cronkite; Invitation of Europe, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_134; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - P. Como - Isaac Stern - Jose Mardones- Kings of the Blues - Margaret Leighton, 04/18/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_397; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - P. Como; A. Williams - I Dood It (Film) - Brecht on Brecht - Voice of Firestone - P. Munsel - Emilio De Gogorza - Sammy Cahn, 04/24/1963; 04/25/1963; 04/28/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_637; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - P. Como; Gen. Pershing - Pope John XXIII - Musicalische Eqequien (Schuetz) This is the life - Leon Campagnola - Gabrielle Ritter - Ciampi, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_643; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - P. Como Mardi Gras - (Boone) Getz - Basie - etc. (American Jazz), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_605; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Pacem in Terris The Premise (TV) Joe Louis (Auto Biog), Inherit The Wind (Film), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_634; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Pagliacci Parsifal Bjoerling - Flagstad, 03/10/1934; 06/22/1951; bell_brothers_tapes_631; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 46)
  - Paradise and the Peri, Robert Schuman; Les Beautitudes, Franck; Alfonso and Estella, Schubert, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_141; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Pardon My Sarong - Cinderella Jones - Billy Budd Britten Incendiary Blonde, 03/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_274; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Paris and Dutch Jazz Festivals in Nineteen fifty two; La Nuit du Jazz, 1952; 12/19/1959; bell_brothers_tapes_608; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 44)
  - Patricia Neway, Il Trovatore songs, Britten Festival, D. D. Eisenhower, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_333; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Paul Scofield and Joy Parker; R. Serkin; Perry Como; Passover Festival, 04/04/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_436; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Pedro Malazarte, Guarnieri; Madeleine Matinetti; Macbeth, Bloch; Martinio di Sant Orsola, Scarlatti; Eliette Schennenberg, Die Abreise, D'Albert, 04/22/1945; 12/16/1945; bell_brothers_tapes_143; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Pelleas and Melisande (Debussy) Odysseus Elytis; George White Scandals; California, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_140; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10)
  - Pelleas and Melisande; Admiral. Byrd; Perry Como; Variations; Chaconne and Finale; Joio, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_543; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Perry Como, 10/25/1961; 11/08/1961; 11/15/1961; 12/06/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_277; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Perry Como - Billy Mitchell, 10/30/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_225; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Perry Como - Bing Crosby Show, 03/16/1960; "bell_brothers_tapes_318 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Perry Como - Bob Hope; Curzon and Britten, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_222; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Perry Como - Casey Stengel, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_221; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Perry Como - Leonard Bernstein in Japan; L'Heure Espagnole, Ravel, 01/17/1962; 01/31/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_348; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Perry Como- Harry Belafonte and Hackett, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_223; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
  - Perry Como Show - Eve Arden; Sarah Vaughn; Guests - (Part 1), 04/06/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_320; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Perry Como Show - Eve Arden; Sarah Vaughn; Guests - (Part 1), 04/06/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_321; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Perry Como - TV, 10/04/1961; 10/11/1961; 10/18/1961; 11/01/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_311; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Perry Como TV Variety, 11/22/1961; 12/20/1961; 12/27/1961; 01/03/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_380; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Perry Como Variety - Perry Como and Bing Crosby, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_317; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Perry Como, Joe McCarthy, Ford; Life Story of Verdi; Claudia Muzio; Joe and Dave, 02/16/1962; 11/21/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_515; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Perry Como - TV Show, 10/03/1962; 10/17/1962; 10/31/1962; 11/07/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_513; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Perry Como; Betty Grable; Brenda Lee, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_063; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Perry Como; Coming of Christ, Dramatization, 04/19/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_328; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Perry Como; J. Garland; Jack Paar Show; Priorities on Parade; Motets; Mendelssohn; Bach, Cantata Magnificant, 12/05/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_536; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Perry Como; Judy Holiday; George Sanders, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_064; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Peter Ibbetson, Deems Taylor, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_058; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 5)
  - Phantom President, G. M. Cohan, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_209; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Phantom President, G. M. Cohan, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_210; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Pigskin Parade, Noel Coward; Perry Como; Lotte Lehmann; Peking Opera; Russell Oberlin; Miscellaneous opera Singers; Death of a Wombat, G. English, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_509; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 37)
  - Pizza Pusher (Goodwin) - (Satire) - Masterwork Chorus - Hamlet (Olivier) - Turandot (Puccini), 05/23/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_426; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 31)
  - PM Program With a Song in My Heart - Jane Froman, 02/17/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_352; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Poliuto Pigmalione both by Donizetti, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_151; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Polly (John Gay) Jules Verne - Blue Skies - (Crosby) - Eternal Waltz (Johann Strauss), 03/31/1963; 04/07/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_596; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Poros (Handel) Road to Singapore - Pinup Girl - Rebel without a Cause, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_359; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Prelude to Pearl Harbor, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_442; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Pres. J. F. Kennedy - 1st Press Conference; State of the Union Message to the Congress, 01/24/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_114; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Pres. J. F. Kennedy - State of the Union Message (Conclusion); Emperor Jones, E. O'Neill, BBC Jennie Tourel; Dietrich Fishe - Dieskau, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_115; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Pres. Kennedy: Parkinson's Law, Hopkins, F. Schorr; Singing guns; Betulia Liberata, Mozart, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_330; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Princesse Jaune, Saint-Saens; Fra Diavolo, Auber; Phryne, Saint-Saens; Sarumba; Jolson Sings Again, Robert Radford, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_699; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Princesse Jaune, Saint-Saens; Fra Diavolo, Auber; Phryne, Saint-Saens; Sarumba; Jolson Sings Again, Robert Radford, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_700; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Processo-a Luculu (Dessau) - Socrate in maginario (Paisielo) Hedda Ga ler (Inser); Love Me Tender, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_671; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 48)
  - Prof. Arnold Toynbee, Noah and Flood, Stravinsky, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_463; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Professor Arnold Toynbee Lectures, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_701; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Professor Arnold Toynbee Lectures, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_702; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Puccini - LA Boheme Metropolitan Jussi Bjoerlino, 12/25/1948; "bell_brothers_tapes_044 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Quartets, Haydn; Op. 17 and Op. 20 Antigone, Anouilb; Music for Millions, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_703; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Quartets, Haydn; Op. 17 and Op. 20 Antigone, Anouilb; Music for Millions, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_704; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 2)
  - Quintet in C Minor (Borodin), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_230; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Radamisto, Handel; Sea Ballads - Opera Excerpts, Spontini; Clara Butt; Miscellaneous Personalities, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_475; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Radio Broadcasts - Paderewski - Taniev - etc., undated; bell_brothers_tapes_586; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
  - Recollections at 30-- Tristia (Berlioz Vaughan Williams) - Cleopatre (Berlio) Riders to Sea - Concertos (Piston - Hindemith)- Paderewski (Piano Rolls) - Al Jolson - Judy Garland in Holland, 01/06/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_378; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Requiem Bellini (Donizetti) - West Point Story - Litaniae (Mozart) The Sea (works), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_394; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - Requiem Mass Verdi - Bienvenuto Cellini Berlioz - Benedicte - Summer Night - Ercole Amante Cavalli, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_695; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Requiem Mass Verdi - Bienvenuto Cellini Berlioz - Benedicte - Summer Night - Ercole Amante Cavalli, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_696; 1/4 inch audio tape (Tray 1)
  - Resurezzione, Alfano; Tito Schipa; F. D. R.; Sara Endich; Electronic Music; Regtime, G. Moore, 03/02/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_563; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Rex Allen; Yehudi Mehuhin: Paganini: Ginger Rodgers - Sir Arthur Sullivans voice, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_362; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Rheingold Bayreuth Festival, 02/22/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_120; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Rheingold Bayreuth Festival; Battle of Cassino, Newsreels of the battles, 02/22/1960; bell_brothers_tapes_121; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 9)
  - Rheingold Walklure - Covent Garden, 1959; bell_brothers_tapes_371; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Rheingold, Metropolitan; Heats On, Mae West; Tale of two Cities, Britten, 12/16/1961; bell_brothers_tapes_387; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 28)
  - Rhythm on the River Film BING CROSBY, 1940; "bell_brothers_tapes_021 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2)
  - Richard Rodgers - WQXR, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_241; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 18)
  - Rickenbacker, etc.; Time out for Rhythm; Perry Como; Ozzie and Harriet; Rick Nelson; Bud and Travis; J. Smith, etc., 06/05/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_624; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 45)
  - Rienzi, Vienna Fest, Flagstad Concerts, Joan Sutherland; Broadway Melody of Ninety Thirty Eight, E. Powell, 1938; bell_brothers_tapes_465; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Rigoletto, Metropolitan, Flutes; P. Como; Air Adventures; K. Rockne; H. Keller; Dag Hammarskjold, 04/05/1961; 11/14/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_572; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Rigoletto; She Done him wrong; Dylan Thomas; MacArthur; Moonlight and Pretzels; A. Mezdahova; Perry Como; Hoover, 10/10/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_546; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Rinaldo Handel Joseph Mehul Le Roid Ys Lalo; L Assasinio Nella Catedrale Pizetti, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_260; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Road to Utopia Crosby - Hope, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_227; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Road to Zanzibar; The Pirate; Johnny Belinda; O Marry Me, Portia Nelson, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_409; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 30)
  - Robert Benchley Film Shorts, undated; "bell_brothers_tapes_047 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Roberta Rose Marie (Part 2), 03/20/0000; bell_brothers_tapes_055; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Roberta Rose Marie (Part 3) and Yom Kippur, 09/21/1958; bell_brothers_tapes_056; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Roberta Rose Marie (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_053; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Roberta Rose Marie (Part 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_054; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4)
  - Romeo and Juliet; Masked Ball, 02/02/1947; bell_brothers_tapes_186; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - Rosa Ponselle, Xmas; Contemporary Music; F. D. R. (Conclusion); St. Mathews Passion, Rehearsal, Stokowski, 03/09/1963; bell_brothers_tapes_565; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)
  - Rosand and Flissler; Huguenots; Copland; McCormack, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_541; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 39)
  - Rosenkavalier, Metropolitan; R. Strauss; Ed Sulliavan Xmas Show in Nineteen sixty two from Guantanamo Bay, 12/22/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_529; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 38)
  - Rossini Lady of the Lake (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_010; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Rossini Lady of the Lake (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_011; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 1)
  - Ruddigore, Gilbert and Sullivan, (Part 1), 04/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_468; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Ruddigore, Gilbert and Sullivan, (Part 2), 04/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_469; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Russalka (Dargominsky) Fedra (Pizetti) - Book with the Seven Seals - Oratorio (Schmidt) Symphony #2 - (Saint-Saens), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_393; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 29)
  - S. Freud - Third Man Igor Gorin - Larry Adler - Works by: Tomasi - Szymanowsky - Pepping, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_598; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
  - Saint Nicolas, Britten, Aldeburgh Festival, 1955; bell_brothers_tapes_472; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 34)
  - Salome (Spoleto Festival) - Jussi Bjoerling - P. Como - Hauptman's Trial, 02/08/1962; 02/09/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_353; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 26)
  - Samson (Handel) Countess Cathleen (Yates) - Lang. Hughes - Gentlemen's Agreement, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_254; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - Samson and Delilah - Metropolitan Op, 12/26/1936; "bell_brothers_tapes_077 "; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 6)
  - San Francisco's Burning, Jepson; Admiraliral Byrd; Serge Koussevitzky; Chista Ludwig, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_448; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 32)
  - Sancta Ludmilla (Dvorak) - Ninon Vallin - Como; Love Me Tonight (Chevalier and J. MacDonald), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_366; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Sancta Ludmilla (Dvorak) - Yehudi Menuhin, 01/06/1962; bell_brothers_tapes_374; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 27)
  - Santa Eufrosina (Malipiero) Socrate (Satie) Carnegie Hall Film Senna Festeggiante (Vivaldi) Young at Heart (Sinatra - Doris Day), undated; bell_brothers_tapes_656; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 47)
  - Sarovan Plays TV - Joan Sutherland - John Gielgud - Patrice Munsel, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_232; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 17)
  - Saul and David (Nielsen) - Il Guarnay (Gomes) Liederkreis - Billy Graham, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_256; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - School for Scandal, Sheridan; N. Kenny, Art Roberts; Vitali; Letters of S. Freud; Sonnambula, Bellini, undated; bell_brothers_tapes_574; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 41)